Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/shivanshsetia-1a479317a (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Python (Programming Language)
Machine Learning Beginner
Natural Language Processing (NLP)

Certifications

Digital Developer Conference:
Machine Learning Track
Introduction to Python
Machine Learning with Python Level 1
Machine Learning
Python for Data Science

SHIVANSH SETIA

Machine Learning Engineer at Arbunize North Delhi, Delhi, India

Summary

A great learner. Coding past 3 years having a great knowledge about python, c and c++ got introduced to machine learning by a friend working hard since then by making projects in this field also did internship training with certification.

Experience

Arbunize
Machine Learning Engineer
March 2020 - Present (1 month)
Delhi, India

RG Smart Discovery LLP
ML Engineer
March 2019 - July 2019 (5 months)
New Delhi Area, India

Education

Indraprastha University
BTech - Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science · (2016 - 2020)

Modern Public School